# Caleb Sanders

795 W Fine Drive, Apt. #D204, South Salt Lake City, UT, 84119 | 530-526-9189 | 97caleb.sanders@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Excellent work history in positions requiring responsibility, initiative, accuracy and confidentiality. Ability to interface effectively with management. Hard working and dedicated to meet the standards expected for the job. Main area of expertise focused around the design and development of websites.

#### **Technical Skills**

CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, C#, NodeJS + ExpressJS Java, Android, ES2015, SASS, AngularJS, React, Python SQL, MongoDB, Google API, ASP.NET MVC, Ruby

### Experience

- Custodian, Florez House Cleaning Services, Red Bluff, CA | December 2013 August 2016
- Student Ambassador, Neumont College of Computer Science, Salt Lake City, UT | February 2017 – September 2017
- Extern, Tribal D, Inc. Native American Self Governance, North Salt Lake, UT | January 2018 - Present

#### Education

Bachelor of Science, Web Design and Development

Neumont College of Computer Science – Salt Lake City, UT – August, 2018

#### **Key Courses:**

Networking, Human Computer Interface and Design, Advanced Web Scripting, Front-End Implementation, Mobile Application Development, Software Projects in Emerging Platforms, Introductory Software Projects, Leadership and Problem Solving, Web-Based Software Projects.

# **Project Highlights**

- Capstone Project Frank Florez House Cleaning
  - Over the course of ten weeks, I designed and a fully-fledged e-commerce site for my previous employer. The site allows the user to easily generate a service order for house cleaning online.
- Advanced Web Scripting Final Activity Hunt
  - This SPA serves to allow users to find activities to do regardless of the weather outside. The purpose of this application is to solve the issue of boredom we experience in our everyday lives.
- Web Based Software Projects Talon

This application serves as a stats tracker for the popular video game Overwatch by Blizzard Entertainments. This application implements an unofficial API for all player data. Developed using ASP.NET MVC and SQL.

# **Additional Information**

## Volunteer Work:

- VFW Post #4218, Corning, CA:
  - o January 2006 September 2015
- CSF, Red Bluff High School, Red Bluff, CA:
  - o September 2011 June 2015